Today's the Christmas Eve
Hurry up
Finish the decorations
Making me work at day again
Speaking of that...
Aren't we also "evil" monsters?
Shall we really gonna celebrate Christmas
Speaking of Christmas
The devil schools didn't have holiday on Christmas
Does this mean that...
Lynn wanted to "purify" us...
During Christmas?!
Ly..
Lynn
You summoned us to your room so mysteriously
For what?
Let's record a video
As a Christmas gift for my brothers
And I got Christmas costume for you
Lynn
Don't be excessive
We evil forces had dignity though
A month of rent free
Let's do this now
Horizontally or vertically
Any make ups required?
Let's get prettier
Well done guys
I got some gifts for you
Under the Christmas tree
Wow~
I think it's useless...
Hot!
Lynn
You must be wanting to purify us
This is terrible
Forgot they can't touch holy stuffs
Just kidding
Tonight
Santa Claus will put the acutal gifts
In your socks
Who were you lying to?
Another gift left
This is so cute
Lynn liked circling so much
Something's wrong
We only had 3 people
But there are 4 cats
This is yours
This is mine
Ira's
And Lynn's
So who sent the gift?
Abu with only 1% of existence
Cheers
Delicious
What a nice day
Let me give you a performance
That's good
Eyes on me
Who are you???
I don't have much skills
Just a simple one
Don't laugh at me
We won't
Very good
Soooo cute!!!
You've been playing this song repeatedly
Could you sing another song
I didn't sing
I was just toning
Wasn't me
Wait
We're all here
So who's singing
It's haunted
Abu
Also felt the happiness of Christmas
Maybe