Madam
The markets at the north
had apples at the price of 4.5
The apples in the supermarket had the price of 3.6
4.9
5.9 and 12.9
According to my investigation
Your apples' quality
is between the apples at the north market and the supermarket
but you had a high price of 5.5
And according to the location and the price
I think it's too expensive
After all it's your right to set your price
But
It's not fair for other markets in All Saints Street
May you could consider my opinion
Stop
4.5 for the apples
OK
An apple please
Just one ???
Troubling me?
WTF
Please wait
Sir
Please fasten your seat belt
When driving on speedways
-2 points
And 50$ for punish
That's all for today's class
Don't run in the corridor
Don't rush with others on buses
Don't go to places with few people
Don't open the door for strangers
Stay safe
Don't do dangerous things
Understand?
I'll go then
See you tomorrow
You just did the most dangerous thing teacher !!!!!!
Welcome back, Lynn
Give me the bag
Must be tired right?
C'mon
Have a sit
Relax
No
Neil
I don't need that
I often do that for my father back in the hell
I'm pretty skiled
Wait
Is this...
Smells good
Don't worry Lynn
You're gonna be RELAXED
What's this
This is hell cleanser gel
It eats dust and virus
Not only for face
And its excretion can keep your skin wet
It's famous in hell
It's...
fine
Isn't it
Ira's words are true
Let me give you a whole body cleanup
No, thanks Neil
You're welcome
C'mon
Lynn
Ira
Is Lynn still angry?
Probably not
Oh yes
(Hic)
L...
Lynn
Sor...
Sorry for yesterday
I just wanted to cook for you
But I made the home a mess
If you don't want me to stay here anymore
I understand
Please forgive me
I knew you were innocent
And I never wanted to drive you away
Really?
Of course
I'm not that kind of angel
Ooooh that's good
The house had been empty for 3 months
If nobody rents it
I'll go broke
But Lynn
How did you put out that fire just in a blink
Ah
Angels' aura
Could purify the evil
Remove illusions
It could be used for daily cleanup
But I'll get a headache if it's used too often
That's so cool
I could show you again
Not a dust
(Sheep Baa)
Sorry
Forgot this also worked for devils