The demon who has ever since young had a love for the human world
Neil Bowman
He has now travelled from Hell
to the human world
With his friends
They started their brand new
Joint rent life
Even so, he was unaware of
a great danger
is eventually
coming towards them
This is your room
I've decorated it for you a bit
You'll like it
Ira
You are so good to me
We were just internet friends
But you still cared about me a lot
Nevermind
Without you
I'll still be stuggling to live
Well, seems like you already forgot
However
It has been three years since that
Uh?The guy who played with me last time...
Now there are two options
I am not sure which to choose
Can you give me some idea?
Choices In-game?                                Choice A
Go back home
Choice B
Stay here
If he went back home
There's no way for the plot to unfold
I choose B
Thanks, Mate
Thats all because of you deciding that for me
So I made up my mind to
Give up inheriting my family's global company and castle
Be a full-time Otaku
It was a serious real-life decision?
Why didn't you tell me clearly?
Now
I don't have to spend hours on makeup before going outside anymore
No more servants and maidens watching me all day
The most important point is
I don't have to go to living room by scooters anymore
I can have instant noodles everyday
Wear T-shirts
No more people messing around me
All thanks to you
Neil
Are you sure your life now is better than before????
Ira
Actually...
Are you OK Ira?
I'm fine
Vampires fall asleep easily during daytime
Cool
Take a look at your room
OK
Like it?
Isn't it like your home
You must be wrong about my home
I've planned this before I came here
I'm going to cook some delicious dish for everyone
You can cook?
Just some home cooking in hell
Simple and delicious
What's this sound
The ingredients
Hell snake and rabbits
You sure we can eat these?
Tastes good
Take this
I also got a lot of seasonings
Ira are you OK?
Oh no
Get back to...
Tips:
In case of emergency
some devils will set themselves on fire subconsciously
Come back
Finally
I...
I'm done
Lynn?
Are you blowing the house up?
What just happend