Dear Mom&Dad
How's the life in hell?
I'm fine these days
My landlord is an angel who's a bit strict
Ira clean up your snacks ASAP
My roommate Ira is an Otaku vampire
Wait a sec
And there's a roommate who's a bit strange
Ira: WTF I'm disconnected
Lynn?!
He's a werewolf
But
It seems that he hates me a lot
He often go out at night
And seems myterious
And...
What happend
He saw the moon on TV by accident
Lynn
Forgive him
Werewolves are sensitive to the moon some days each month
You brought him back
You clean this up with me later
Or more rent
What???
Wait
Why it's my business?!
And...
NEVER let him see anything round
On The days before full moon
Or
Something terrible happens
One more time you morph at home
You say goodbye to this house
Why it's covered?
It's out
Covered again?!
It's out!
Trolling me??
I can't morph until dawn...
Maybe I should go home now
In case anyone see me in this form
Uh?!
Where's my bag?
My bag!
Pervert! Call the police!
psychotic
Better to wait for the moon
Damao?
You okay?'
It's deep
Baby moles down there
We can only dig them out
Dig it
Nevermind
We can't destroy their home just for clothes
You were such a kind man Damao
You can speak Chinese???
So is it?
Uh..
Damao
I wasn't meant to follow you
But you just ran away from home
I was worried
Thank you
Here
Wait for me
Let me find a pair of  trousers for you
I'll be back soon
Why didn't he come back...
Rogue!
I'm not!