Stupid Lynn
nagging me all day
Can't you just buy it online?
Also what does he mean by keeping an eye out for any new tenants?
As if that is something you just stumble across during a walk
What are they looking at
that feels good
What a good boy!
Whose dog is this?
Here, have one more (sausage)
Isn’t it dangerous without a leash on though
Tch, thought it was something important
Looks like he’s been a stray for a long time
Look he’s even got scars
Just a werewolf
Let’s take him to get neutered first
We should send him to the rescue centre
Hey big boy
gramps has food if you follow me
Look it's food
Sorry
this is my dog.
He broke off the leash and ran away
It've been trying to find me for hours
If you don’t want to be neutered then follow me.
This is the new tenant I found
A Northern werewolf
His name is too long so I don't remember it
Just call him Damao
Werewolves...
Do they usually shed a lot
Where's Neil
He's playing outside
Said that he wanted to get familiar with the area.
Alright
Then you just have to do the introductions later
Let's go
Let me show you around
Vampires and werewolves...
Weren't they enemies?
Come in and take a look
This room is awesome!
It is good though
But it still had some pest problems
Pest problems?
If you really want to live here
Clean it up
I think I've been underestimated
Even pests dare to pick on me
Got 'em
Well done
These two things always mess with me in my room
What a trouble
Luckily you werewolves aren’t afraid to get a bit messy
YOUR room?
You lied to me!
I never said that was your room
We are roommates now
roommates helping each other out isn’t such a big deal
Your room is the first one to the left upstairs
Hurry up
This is your room
I'm going to work
Don't knock at my door at night
So when the day
If you need anything ask Lynn
Bye
And these
They are yours now
I couldn't belive it...
They’re really letting me stay here
Yeah
Amazing!
I'm finally lucky now
Hello
You're Damao right?
I am your next-door neighbour
My name is Neil Bowman
Just call me Nini
You...
You're the dark lord
You alright?
Ira
Lynn
Damao has fainted!
It seems my luck
truly hasn’t turned