Hey,sister, what would you like to have
Mom, I want this
Let me see
Neil
What are you thinking of
Coming back this late again?
We still had many customers today
Where is he working?
I'm going to sleep
Good night
Always come here with scars
Is he really OK?
Wh..
What are these???
Neil
I can give you money if you need
PLEASE don't work for there anymore OK?
W..
Why?
Though I'm only a temporary worker
But I enjoyed it very much
You..
ENJOYed it ?!
What do you think he's doing
A pet shop?
Are these things really pets?
You guys are so naughty
Why did he enjoy it ?
Look out !
That was dangerous
But you're fine
Be careful in the future
Neil
Looks like you've grown up
Why are you still laughing?
The animals had escaped
Thank you
Ira
But...Why're you here?
Uh...I was just passing by
And saw these animals
They're all so lovely
Aren't they?
They're so lovely
This is Cheng Huang
You could live longer if you ride on it
Would you like to try that?
No,thanks
This one is cute
Why's he always scratching on his neck
Is the necklace to tight for him
Let me help you
Ira, don't !
Ira----------
This is Bie Bie
It will dry out all the water nearby
And it could cause a drought sometimes
Your
Working environment
Is so bad
If I didn't stay here
Nobody cares about them
As long as they're healthy
I'll be satisfied
And
I LOVE cute animals
This touch
This size
Enough
Who won't like it ?
I'm almost bald
I think this is why you liked this work
I'll stay here FOREVER
If you like