This is the kingdom of snow in the far north
Where wild werewolves lived peacefully
I'm summoning you here
To make an important announcement
We got a message from the World Werewolf Organization
The dark lord who's going to ruin the world is rising
To maintain world peace and our glory
We're going to send a volunteer
To get more info about the dark lord
Head
Are you kidding me
To spy on the dark lord all alone
That's no difference from death
I agree with him
Disagree!
So
Let's make it fair
Let's draw
That's OK
Better than that
Let's continue
Head you're so smart
Wait!
Damao
Don't worry
We'll remember you
I didn't draw yet
The ticket is ready
7p.m today
Why it has to be me
Get on
I'll get you to the station
Shut up
Let's follow the program
Damao
You go first
Save some time
(Laughter)
What are you laughing for
Stop it
It can't be me
Why--------
I knew that there were thieves
So I put 30kg of iron in my bag
Ahh
I'll be back
Neil
Is this kid really the dark lord
Pretty far from here according to the map
I bought this water-proof phone for this
I knew that electronic devices aren't reliable
Do you think I only got one?
Wait a sec bro
I didn't expect to use it so soon
Where's plan C?
Oh D
You again?
It's terrible here...
Why I'm out of luck
Why the mission was on me
Don't they worry about my life
(Lyrics)
Why so many people here
Seems like they can really fight
I'd better leave here
Moon
I'm...
I'm done