Episode 22:  All money is spent on this episode
Neil!
What
Who am I, where am I
Good job, Nick
What are you doing
Is this
What
To get the dark lord's power
Raise this wand and say the spell
Show your power dark lord
And come to me now
Nick
You dare to betray us?
He did this on proposal
Look at Neil!
I...
I did it?
Finally
I got the power of the dark lord
So annoying
So disgusting
Go die!
Don't come here!      So annoying
These noise...                    Get away!
Are...
Don't talk anymore!
Don't...
Don't
No!
Can't see anything...
Neil
No
Something's wrong
It's the dark lord
Dark lord?
What are you waiting for?
Fight!
Again
Why always bothering me
I just want to sleep
Stop talking
People who chosen by you
Either die
Or went mad
You're still pretending that you're innocent
They're too weak
Just some negative energy
You can't blame me when they couldn't handle it
Now!
Success?
No...
It's ended?
Just noobs
Let's continue the topic
I found out after so many tries
Neil is different from you
What
Neil?
He's like a black hole
Absorbs all of my negative energy
Thanks to him
I could sleep well
Enjoy a peaceful life
Days like these
Were runied by you
So I could only kill all of you
Fight back!
Target is too small
Can't hit him
Damn
Why didn't he become bigger
Because giants must be dead
What
Back!
Fall back!
Want to leave now?
I'm afraid it's a bit late
You're really not a usual angel
Give Neil
Back to us!