Episode 15:  How to be a nice brother
I Remembered
When Neil was in primary school
Now we practice fighting in two
Teacher
I want to be with Neil
Neil is mine
Go away
Mine mine                                  Pick me!
I'm so welcomed
What's the matter with you
Always being so sad <!--Need better translation>
I'm always the one who got sandbagged in sports class
Why didn't you tell me?
I'll handle this
Don't worry
Class
Now practice in twos
Teacher
I'll be with Neil
Why a senior high school student came to primary school?
So nobody else will hurt you
Nick
Hahaha
I'm still better than you
Teacher!
Neil is dying
Since then
We often play together
Enjoyed it?
We play wrestling
Darts
Home run!
And things like baseball
Our relationship is getting better
He started collecting my cool photos
Neil's desperately wanted to possess me
Regarding a doll as me
Neil is so lonely without me
Make drinks for me carefully
Neil's drink for me made with love
I missed these so much...
Stop it
I let you retell things happened last night
Not your whole life
You also had a sister
Could you understand it
The rebellious phase
Brother
I brought breakfast for you
No
Totally don't
E...
Sorry, everyone
Yesterday Nick
My brother caused trouble to you
Uh?
He's did it totally on purpose
What?
Neil
Stay away from him
Weird
Couldn't recall things happened last night
I just knew
Ira you can really fight<!--Couldn't translate directly, translated by alternate meanings. Need change>
Of course I can
Remember it
I'm born in a vampire family
I'm pure blood werewolf
Anyway
He shouldn't show up anymore
Uh???????
Why are you here?
I brought him here
He made the house a mess
Replace furniture
Cleanup
Buy stock
Continue
Still not over?
Didn't we make a deal?
To recover the home from your trouble
You're responsible for all the business
That's too much
You're such a devil
I give up
Pardon?
I said I give up
Just kidding
Just keep going
Such a troublesome angel
But gave me a excuse to stay here
All caused by the damn dark lord
Now I've fallen this low
I can only wait
And collect intel<!-- need a word to replace information>
As for now
Let's get back to the old work <!--Alternate meaning, may change>
Sir <!-- Dunno how to call him>
Had such a rotten soul since young
Consider going to hell?
Join us now and get a free bath in the pots for the first month
And a hellhound
What are you wating for?
Forgive me!
I know I'm wrong!
The police did a great job recently