Episode 15:  With The Right Conditions And Initiative, Trash Can Turn Into Treasure
We're offline?
Lynn!
Because of the power failure
Will recover in 3 hours
I see
3 hours                         Just for 3 hours
3 HOURS?
You're so noisy
It's only been 10 minutes!
Couldn't you just calm yourselves down?
No
Oh
Your halo can generate electricity right?
Can we use it?
It's not for using like this!
Is this really good?
Better than heatstroke
It's so hot
that I woke up
Why is it so cool outside?
You
What are you guys doing
There's some smell
Would it be...
There's really a smell...
Is there?
Really...
My blood creams are melted
Why not give electricity for the fridge?
My soul creams escaped!
So unreasonable!
All things in the fridge is melted
The fridge uses too much electricity
The halo's power is not enough
So why you turned on the AC?
The air conditioner is the most important in the hottest days
So is the Internet
Shut up
You're using our Wi-Fi <!--Need change>
I didn't save it!
Is he...
Going to transform?
No
He's just unlucky as usual
How unlucky is he
Everytime he's picked to wash the dishes
Hit by a ball when lying on his bed
Only a pair of pants left after he returns
That's really unlucky
Unlucky...
What
Don't bother me for nothing
Damao
Do you want to buy some...
Wait
I'm not advertising
Listen to me
Oooooooouch
I tell you
They're on TV
Welcome to the super 666 show
The challengers this time is Damao and Nick
They're going to pick one golden egg which contains 2 million RMB from ten
Can they be successful?
Let's wait and see!
I'm going to pick...
1,2,3,4,6,7,8,9,10
THEY GOT IT!
Are you sure you're going to buy insurance for "car crash caused by being hit by a ball"
The probability of this accident
Stop asking
I said buy it
Return to base!
Hurry up!
Out!
Must make sure he
and his limited edition shirt untouched
No worry
We're professional
Nick you're the best
I misunderstood you
Of course