Episode 15:  Don't worry when there's only a few things <!--How to tl this properly>
What?
My drink
My popcorn
Unless...
WTF IS THIS
Damao
You hair shedding
Get out
Where's he?
He went to attend the dacing competition
What?
Wait
If Lynn sees this...
You invited him
Your responsibility
Seems it's all on my own....
Finally it's done
And then...
The pile of hair
It's a waste to just throw it away
Aha
I'm back!
I got the "aunts' favorite" prize
They say it's the first prize!
Really?
Congratulations
Why is it so familiar...
AHHHHHHHHH——
My my
My hairline had receded again?
WHY?
Why????
Although I sleep late and get up early every day
Sleep during day and awake at night
Eat snacks as meal
Are you done?
Streaming all day
I need a bath
My hair shouldn't lose so fast
It's so hot
Got to much hair
Had to go to pet shop to get a haircut
I should get a VIP card last time
Damao
Look!
A big bone!
Where?
No!
I'm just a dog if I don't resist <!--Need better tl>
Why are you still awake?
Whaaaaat do you want to do?
This is the hair-restorer Lily brought from heaven<!--Google tl, is this or "pilatory"better?>
Uh
I was too excited when I picked your hair
This
Take it
You're apologizing to me?
It's pretty expensive
Don't waste it
Feel free to tell me
if you want to buy something in heaven
Damao
I heard you've been using hair-restorer recently
How is it?
Very effective
That's too effective
(Laughter)
Your hair is long enough
Now it's harvest time
Ira you bastard
I knew you were apologizing to me on purpose
Your hair is useless except for selling
Would you mind if I cut it off?
Don't touch my hair!
Come on