Episode 14:  Nothing is the best
Ira
What's the matter with you two?
Stop fighting
Back off!
He's not Ira anymore
That's right
He's mine now
Nick?
Why are you here?
He's 100 times more evil than before
Go
Really 100 times more evil...
Follow him
The strangers are gone
Now we can have a talk
Neil
You're coming for me right?
Why you're hurting my friends?
Huh?
Friends?
(Laughter)
You're as stupid as usual, brother
Nevermind
Right into topic
I wasn't coming for you
I'm coming for him
Simple ways to
awake the dark lord
Nick
You...
​still haven't outgrown your chūnibyō phase yet...?
No it's you
What a pity...
Shut up and cooperate
You're already so old...
Let me see...
I see...
OK!
Let's start with the first method
What are you gonna do
No sign of awakening...
Try the second one
And the 3rd
4th
5th
6th
None of the 99 methods worked...
Let me check what's the very last one
And play the audio
Scan the QR code below
Seriously?
Probably it won't work either
Ha
Finally it worked?
​Oh no
He's gonna kill me
What's the matter? Summoning me in the middle of the night
Hello, your majesty
I'm
I know
Neil's brother
Hurry up and give a word
Or I'm going to sleep
Your majesty
I wish to make a deal with you
And that's all of my thoughts
​It's beneficial to both of us.
I'd like to hear your thoughts
I only have one question
Please go ahead
You're really something, huh?
Who do you think you are?
Dare to deal with me?
Waking me up means you're ready to die
Right?
Disappear
We're home!
Uh?
Hey
Police office?
No
We had a thief in our home
It's not like that
Listen to me!       Address is All Saints Street