Episode 32:  How much surprise that I didn't know
Oh, why didn't Ira come
He'll be damaged by the sun
Next
I'll be with Lily next
Should I sit in the front
Don't be afraid, hold me close
Neil
Or should I sit in the back
Don't worry, I'm here
Neil
So hard to decide...
We're next
Let's go
Next
Here
That's awesome!
Let's do this again. Luis
Luis?
Somebody help! Somebody died
Luis
Lynn
Could you go to another pool for a moment
What's the matter
You and Lily had turned all the water in the pool into holy water
So where should we go then
I got a good idea, follow me
Can't you swim, Neil
Lily
I couldn't learn it
I'll teach you
Really? I will try my best
But
If I'm in the same pool as you
I'll turn into a goat
No problem, leave it to me
Listen to my instructions!
Move your feet like flip-flap and swing your arms like woosh
Can't...
And one, two, one, two
Understand it
Isn't that Neil
Being a part-time lifeguard
Hold on
Your brother is coming to rescue
Stay away from me
Don't be afraid, Neil
Stay away
I'm rescuing you
Neil learns so fast
Hello
We are holding summer activity for lovers here
If you're alone...
No
They aren't lover...
Oh Lynn
You didn't even wait for me
We're couple
Could we come in
Come in please
Thanks for the help
But I didn't mean to lie...
Why are you so polite
It's me
Surprised?
Transformation is an optional course in Devil University
And Neil couldn't become such a beauty like me
Are you shy?
Just deceptive tricks
Why would I be shy
Who was deceptive
Those are real
Touch it if you don't believe me
Pervert
Why did you slap me
Abu
We're leaving
How long has he been here?
Won't he become soak?
But it seems he really likes bathing
Maybe he had some kind of Egyptian magic
It's really magic?