Episode 31:  Worker Wolf with a Worker's Soul!
5 o'clock in the morning
While Neil is still in a tender sleep
Ira finished his stream for today
And Abu just got up
Lynn is busy preparing breakfast
Nick
Luis is practicing as usual
A Chinese tongue-twister for practising standard Mandarin
And Damao, began his first dance in the morning
He was supposed to
He
Is still working overtime
Nothing special
A week ago
Just make me feel right
4 days ago
Just a little closer
Adjust it again
2 days ago
Still a little weird
Now
This is...
I still think the first version was the best
Calm down, Damao
Amitabha Buddha I must pass
Amitabha Buddha
This one looks good to me
I've finally done it
I'm going to take a bath, have a meal and danc...
Wait a second
Let our boss review it
"Assistant Liu" invited "Boss X" to the chat group
Hello
I have time
Ok
Go on
Only this one?
I'll have it done right away
Send
Completely different from what I expected
Can't explain my thinking clearly on the phone
Come over for a meeting today
You're here
I think this draft
I think
Please continue
I think this draft is pretty good
Just this... this one
Really
Looks like it's more efficient to talk face to face indeed
Ye... Yeah
5 o'clock in the evening
Neil finished his work in the pet shop
See you tomorrow, boss
Ira got up and started to wash up
Damao
Could you make a logo for my channel if you have time
Abu and Laofu
Damao
Since you're here
Lynn is busy preparing dinner
Make a PPT for me while you're at it?
I need it for my public class next time
Luis just came back from the film set
Damao
Please make a resume for me
And Damao
Started his first dance in the evening
He was supposed to
Damao
Could you help me with...
PPT design: 60￥/hour
Resume layout: 1000￥/hour
Logo design: 300￥/hour
Poster design: 400￥/hour
Others 200￥/hour
Never mind
Damao
I just wanted to ask, about our payment...
Our company went bankrupt and closed down
And...
Could you return the deposit to us?
Damao
Are you still there
Delicious
Right