Episode 33:  Happy birthday
Ira didn't wash the dishes this week, minus 10 points
Damao hides his hair under the sofa, minus 3 points
Happy birthday, brother
I'm the first one to greet you again this year
It's this day again
Happy birthday, brother
I planned for a birthday party
This is the flow chart and program list of the party
Only the first part
Thank you Lily, I got your greetings
You don't have to celebrate my birthday this year
Just a brief celebration?
No
Seems Lily really didn't set it up
Now I can relax myself
I'm back
Ira
Come on, come on, come on
Nobody remembers today is my birthday?
Just do it like this to pass that level
Do you know what day is it today?
I thought you'd never ask
You won't get any gift from me just because today is Teachers' day
You are not my teacher anyway
No one really remembers my birthday...
Brother
I'm sorry
I still want to hold a birthday party for you
Today is Lynn's birthday?
You are such a troublemaker
It's up to you
Don't worry, brother
I prepared a very simple one this year
Come on
Nice
Really much simpler this year
How complex was it before?
And I wrote a song for you, brother
I sent it to your phone
Happy birthday
Thank you Lily
I'll make it my ringtone later
I got here on time
Happy birthday, Lynn
This is a gift I just brought from abroad
The newest vacuum cleaner
We don't have anything to give, what should we do
Give anything we have
Happy birthday Lynn
Here's a diary of this year
Two-thirds of the year has passed
Yeah
So I ripped them off for you
Happy birthday Lynn
A dog bowl for you
Isn't this your bowl
Lynn, this hell dirt...
Keep it for yourself
Out of the way
Lynn
Here's new clothes for you
Happy birthday
What's this
Get these off
Don't do that
And I have a free makeup for you
I don't need that
I know you all forgot today is my birthday
You don't have to bother yourself for the gift if you don't have one
I'm already happy if you make less trouble every day
Lynn
You are so busy in the past year
We won't do this in the future
Don't say that if you can't do it
Could we...
Let's make an exception today
Hooray
It's their happiness
I got nothing
I will definitely not celebrate my birthday next year