Episode 28:  Who wants to be single?
Lynn
The movie is starting soon, Lynn
Lynn just left
Don't know what he's going for
He's dressing up pretty well
My brother is on a date
Oh he was dating
Dating?
He says she's introduced by the landlord of 1031
He must go
Lynn is so boring
So unfortunate for that girl
You have no reactions at all?
What's the point
They're just having a date
Who cares
Let's go, Lily
Let's have a meal in Lynn's restaurant
Show me the way
Ok
You care about this...
And everyone's here
Four
There
You're so humorous Lynn
Where
I've never seen anyone say my brother's humorous
Nevermind
Let's see who's that
That's Jiuyue
You know her?
I've seen her once before
I've never thought I'd see her again here
The world is soo small
To be honest
I'm a fox spirit over 200 years old
And I rarely had a date
I thought I'm going to be single forever
How's that possible
Though we've just met
But I feel happy to be with you
You must have lots of people who like you around
Don't say that, I'm embarrassed
Do you need to order
Any recommendations?
The servant is pretty special
Looks tasty
Cheese
Abi is so handsome
That durian ice cream is pretty good
Oh yes
How long do you want to stay there
Lynn
What's your job
I'm a doctor and a teacher
Teaching English and Chinese
That's awesome
No wonder your English is so good
I'm poor at English
Oh no
Excuse me?
There's no bad students
Only bad teachers
Spend some time to finish these tests
I'll give you special plan based on your skill
I grantee your language level will dramatically improve
And come to my class
Improve further
I'll give you 10% off
Consider it
That's terrible
Lynn how could you be like that
The date becomes a class promotion
Jiuyue's basics...
How did you know
I just remembered I had a draw
My fans are waiting, bye
Something wrong with your neck?
Yeah
I was...
I had a stiff neck
This guy...