My head aches
Was I drunk again
Clothing is fine
And woke up at home
So probably nothing happened yesterday
Though I didn't remember
What happened
Someone broke into here?
Anyone
Lynn
She's here again
You
Stay back
One step ahead and I'm done with you
Why
Stay back
Let's talk outside
I will send a bill of damaged items to your email
Anyway before you quit drinking
Don't come to 1031 again
What
I broke all of that?!
Above all
Lily will live with you these days
As a supervisor
Hello, Momo
So thank you
Lily should be asleep now
Now
Lily you underestimated me so much
Don't drink alcohol
Lily is watching you
How did you find me
Lily, Momo
I'm here with condolences
Is Momo ok
Hasn't drink any alcohol for two days
I'll put juice and desserts on the desk
Who is this
Looks familiar
That's the photo of me when I was an idol
Idol?
Hello everyone
We are
Then why did you give up
It's too stressful to be an idol
But it's mainly my habit is difficult to change
And I was photographed on the headlines
How did they recognize you
The reporter is so powerful
Then I wanted to change a environment
And start fresh
So I was here
You are so brave to start fresh
Cheer up, Momo
You will finally quit drinking
Thank you
Come on
Let's drink the whole box
Drink until you're drunk
Where's Lily
Why Lily isn't watching her
Lily
Together
Cheers
How did this happen
It's the drink I bought
It contains alcohol?
We're all drinking
Now it's your turn
With the effort from Lynn and all members of 1031
Momo
Finally succeeded in quiting drinking after a year
But the
Nobody ever wanted to talk about it again