Episode 26:  Frightening Halloween
The lord is already inside
He has been waiting for a long time
What
Don't do that!
Shut up
I can't even hear the lines
Who's that
It's midnight
I'll open the door
I'm back
Did I went to the wrong door
Luis
Ira
My name is Luis
Just call me Lulu
I always had a dream
To become a film star
But at my hometown
The job is so boring
So I decided to leave my home
To find a job here
80yuan a day, need a crowd actor
Choose me
I had experience of 12 films
I'm the universal crowd actor
My head!
It's fine
I couldn't be an actor if it was broken
Hey
Bro
Beside your head
Can you also take off other parts of your body?
I... got caught by gangsters
Ye...Yes
I haven't become famous yet...
I'm not ready to die...
You're chosen
It's an important role
Do your best
They're not gangsters
Scene 13, take 1
Fire!
We've come so far
We're the only two left
No matter how difficult it is
We can't lose
Give me a hand
No problem
We'll go over this together
Abi
I know you'll say it
Let's go
Cut
Excellent
Props, prepare for next scene
Come on, Abi
Let's fight them to the death
Yeah, that's it
We got surrounded
Damn
I'll cover you, Abi
You go first
Damn
Why did you come back
There's no point in leaving without you
Not bad for you
We'll travel the world after this
I promise
Abi
Wake up
Wake up!
We're almost there
Why
Abi became famous right after that
I had to left 1031 for half a year to follow them
My god
Abi was discovered in this way
Give me a signature
That's not the focus