Episode 25:  A friend of my friend is also a friend of mine... or is it?
Dear mom and dad
How's it going in hell
I'm fine living here
Recently
There's someone who I care about
I'm coming
She's the person I like
Though I haven't expressed her my feelings to her yet
But I'm already happy with this
Since I can stay with her all day
Besides
The dark lord inside me has released most of his energy
The Dark Force Union could no longer sense his existence
I'm not a timebomb anymore
Who still write diaries now
Not a diary!
It's an email!
No
Don't look at it!
Didn't we agreed you should stay inside me
and don't bother each other
Girls don't like nagging boys
You... be careful
Lily
Lily is back!
Beware of others who are ahead of you
Lily
They still didn't made peace?
You're back...
Oh
How are classmates in heaven doing?
Everyone's the same as before
Lily
You have no idea how much I've missed you
The class got so boring since you left
Maybe you should stay for a few more days
I made lots of interesting friends
You'll like them
It's Neil
This is Evan
My best friend from Heaven University
Hello Neil
Call me Evan
You're so shiny
What's that
I've never had one
Let me show you
It's both fun here and there
They fit so well together
Let's go to have some meal first
I can't even have a word
Still relying on me
You three inside please
Our signature dish Stinky Tofu
Please enjoy
I've got the bill
Evan have some more
Make fool of him publicly when possible
This will make you look a bit better
This...
This taste...
is so delicious
Next
Soybean juice
Nice
A dish of preserved eggs
Yummy
Snail Noodles
Awesome
May I have a takeout
I'm full
A takeout for snail noodles
Go on
Hurry up
Alright
Let's go there next
Lily
Wait for me
Neil
You alright?
I'm fine
Thanks
Neil
If Lily couldn't live happily here
I must take her back to heaven
This was my thought before I came here
But I won't think of it anymore
Seems she has made the right choice
To have a good friend like you
I'm happy for her
Evan
Thanks for staying with me these days
This
Is a small gift
Evan is so good
He had a gift for me while thinking of Lily
I'm so sorry with what I did
Neil, come on!
I'm going to sleep
Sorry for the bother