Episode 29:  Don't touch random stray cats
Stop barking, move!
Move!
Isn't this...?
Ira
Come look at this
I found a kitty downstairs
It has two tails
So unusual
Isn't this...?
I want to keep it
But I don't know if Lynn would allow it
What a strong stink of alcohol
First of all
It's a nekomata, not a cat
Second
It's our next-door neighbor in 1032
You'd better put it back
Before it wakes up
In the corridor?
Will it get lost?
And it hasn't woken up for so long
Did it pass out?
Who are you
Why is it so aggressive
And did it just speak?
Now you're learning something, Nini
Nekomata are cat spirits from Japan
Pretty normal that it speaks
Don't run around
That's my Lafite '82
Damao's Vodka
No! Lynn's red wine
It's... drunk
Oh no
It drank too much alcohol
We must take it to the hospital
It turned into a woman?!
Told you it's our next-door neighbor
He... Hello?
What are you doing
Why am I always the one who gets hurt
She's on my bed
What should I do
Let her be
Can't let her sleep on the floor
Just don't let Lily know about this
Put the phone down
What are you doing
Nick
Why are you here
You're finally a man
I don't know her at all
My poor little kitty
I can't believe Neil left you hanging like this
So share the night with me, Nick, instead
Stay away
I'm so sorry
I'm really sorry
I caused so much trouble for you yesterday
I'm terribly sorry
I'll buy you replacements for what I drank yesterday
I'm very sorry. It's fine
Get up first
Drunk Damao is much scarier than you
But you should drink less in the future
Excessive drinking is too harmful to the body
So I'll introduce myself again
My name is Momo, I live in room 1032
I'm a warzone journalist
This is Sake, from my homeland
To make amends for what happened last night
Please accept it
I'll take it then
Please...
Take it!
Nevermind
I'll get you a better one next time
You really don't have to
Could you please drink it at home