Episode 27:  Panic as the house get crowded
This is a scene from "A Song of Blood and Brain"
A play with the vampire queen
This is "The Last Days"
It's a climax part I acted
It's so amazing
This video is the part I had a line in "The Bad Omen"
Work is over for now
Finally I can live here again
About this
Luis
1031 has no empty room left
The room I used to live
Now Neil lives there
I remember there was a room beside it
Damao lives there
That's fine
How?
Lynn
How about letting Luis sleep on the sofa like last night
No
It's ok for one night
But long term is unacceptable
What about living in the fridge
His body could be stored separately
No
Fridge is for food only
Put it outside?
It also protects against moisture
Is he actually living
You sure?
Abu
Forget about it
It's too small for you to live with me
It's okay, my room is pretty big
Speaking of it
We've never seen Abu's room before
Let's go and have a look
I'm opening
What the hell is that
I've listened to the cards
Your grandpa I
Sorry, wrong door
You even had a pet?
Is that the point?
Again
Nope
Not this
What was that
This time for sure
What a great room
You can put your coffin here
And
Take the key
Abu
Luis
How can I thank you
No... I don't need that
It's so inconvenient to live together
That's ok, Luis
No
It's too much bother for you
I really don't need that
Fine
Couldn't you insist for a bit?
Why would you be polite about such things?!
Wha...
What's this
What's happening
Someone broke into our house
Luis is right