Episode 13:  I came from sky with lightning
Damao, Ira
We have...
What's happening???
It all begins like...
Scan for household service
What the heck is this
Trash ads
Why is it so tiring to get home...
Finally no more ads
Really troublesome
AGAIN
Fine
I'll scan it anyway
Just like this?
Really came here?
Dear customer
Nick, Devil No.2698 at your service
So delicate...
Wait
Devil?
Sir
I just checked your profile
Profile?
Wait
I just scanned your QR
You don't have any criminal record despite being a vampire
Using your family's money for house rent and expenses
And spent a lot
Never had a work longer than half a year
Called yourself a famous streamer
But had less than ten thousand followers
And few reward
I'm not willing either...
Ira
Stop suppressing yourself
Now it's a good change to work for Satan
You will show yourself after joining us
Stop talking
And nobody will say you rely on your family
You'll honor your family
Live your life as you want
Easy
But
Let's say hello to our fellow first
Shall we?
Is this...
Yes
I'm your fellow
Devil Nick
We noticed the dark lord is awaking
And sent me to stop him from destroying the world
Assist me
With your power and information
Let's defeat the dark lord
Are you Ira's friend
Again
You are here to defeat Neil...
...defeat the dark lord?
What
Did you forget the reason you came here
Of course I didn't
Anyway
Bring me to the dark lord
What do you mean?
Wasn't fighting the universal language?
I mean
DONT'T HURT NEIL
How will you report to the werewolf council
Say that you betrayed them?
I'll report the truth
I'm here
How could I leave you behind?
There's no dark lord here
Is Neil so powerful that
He made a werewolf retreat
Because he did a free SPA for me yesterday
You're way too easy to buy over...
So you won't cooperate
So I'll do it with force
Ira?
Let me see the bloody battle between werewolf and vampire!
So I'll be in the next episode?