Dear brother
How are you?
I'm living happily in heaven
Got a nice grade in all subjects
Of course
I didn't forget to develop sports
But I was caught doing paper work in art class
And ask me to rethink about it
But after I thought about it carefully
I'm all alone
Where's my home
Lily
So I came for you
Brother
Anywhere you are is my home
Love you~
Get back now
Let me introduce to you
This is my sister Lily
Hello everyone
She transferred to a school here recently
She'll live with us till school starts
You should watch her learn Chinese
Don't play everywhere
Is this sister Lin from heaven
I guess she's gonna be twice as strict as Lynn
She's coming to us
Wow
Are you really a werewolf?
Can you morph?
Can I watch you when you morph next time
Wow Mr.Vampire you're so handsome
Especially your hat
It matches really well with your eyes
Thanks
This is the first time I've seen a real devil
It's so lovely
Tell me something about hell at your spare time
So many people(spirits?) here
And it's so lively
I'll have a hotpot today
Tomorrow I'll climb the great wall
Watch the comic dialogue
I'll order the seats
Can't you understand what I'm saying
Don't know how's Lily going on with them
Did she studied well
Lily, today...
Lily danced with me today
And played many video games with me
Saw the panda with me
Abu's beauty ingredient is so mystery
Lily
You're getting familiar with them
I'm so pleased
Did you finish your homework
Oh Neil
I was always curious about the schools in hell
Are they funnny
Nothing's really funny
We did a lot of exercise since we were young
To make your will strong
Like pushing old people
Harder
Neil
More harder
I told you to practice pushing old people
Not massaging for me
Destroying plants
Finally completed
I let you destroy it not make it more perfect
And paint things on others' walls
Teacher
I've filled the whole wall
Neil please stop it
I beg you
Really missing the time back then
But
No matter how hard I've worked
I can't do evil things
Maybe I can't be considered as a devil
We are alike
Others always tell me
"You're nowhere like an angel"
But that's myself
Why must I be like other angels
So in my opinion
Neil is Neil himself
Hard-working
Kind-hearted
And is good at doing nice things
Aren't you also a handsome devil?
Nobody...
Ever said anything like this to me
Lily