I love you too
Neil
Here's your package
Ok
What's this
Such a heavy one
What is love
Is 'fall in love at first sight' real
100 skills to confess
Psychology about love
XX tell you how to get GF
Skills about dating
Neil
Having trouble these days?
N...No
Why I'll get any trouble
Feel free to talk to me when needed
Actually
One of my friend
Fell in love with someone
So
He wanted to know how to be famous
Oh...
Speaking of this
I was pretty famous back in England
Please tell me how?
You slipped your tongue...
I'm on it
First
Change your old-fashioned outfit
Then make a romantic atmosphere
And move her with your luxury taste
Ready to go in any moment
At last
Hug her deeply
And give her a bite on her neck
Just kidding
I failed disguising...
Did you just find it out...
Lily,I got something important to tell you, can we (Not typed) tonight
Lily, Ira gave me two discount coupons of a five-star restaurant, shall we
Stop hesitating
Just send it
I sent the half message I didn't finish!
What?
OK!
Let's have dinner together
Replied in seconds???
Didn't you go to dance every night, Damao?
You can send him there
Me?
Gonna be late...
Just ran out of luck on the way
No fuel
Road in construction
Car accident
Uh?
We're arrived
She is....
No
I'm going to... (Neil:You okay?)
Don't mind me
Damao
Go away!
Quickly!
How can I leave you behind?
Lily
Neil
Sorry
I was late
So we...
It's closed
Sor..
Sorry
So, we're going to another one!
OK
Waiter
Two bowls of noodles
OK
Coming!
Your clothes today is really cool!
Is it?
Thank you, Lily