Episode 12:  Happy new year, happy new year, we wish you a happy new year
I failed confessing last time
And my relationship with Lily became more awkward
I'm going to some crowded place for relaxing
Why you're here at this time
We're all going back to our hometown for the new year
New..
New year?
It's new year now!
Let's have some fireworks
He's way too excited...
Came outside the sixth ring
I bought some fireworks
Let's play them together
What's your definition of "some"
Neil
That's not funny at all
Let me show you
What's that
Your reaction is too..
Oh no
Don't burn them, Neil!
Stop it!
That's so cool
The temple fair is crowded
Don't get lost..
Ira,come here
Here's your favorite food
Mom, Dad
Are you living good these days?
Everything's OK here
It's winter here
I'm wearing coats now
Don't worry about me
My roommates are great
10 score
They all have amazing skills
They're like brothers
Letting me know about this totally different world bit by bit
All of these made me felt mysterious and beautiful
Sorry
The shops are closed
I went to a further place to buy them
Finally you're back
Don't rush
We're all waiting for you, the dumplings are just out
The new year is coming
The food is various
Hope you're here too
We share the stories of me and my friends together
Missing you
Please don't worry
I'm living happily
Love you, Neil