Dear leader
Since the day I came to All Saints Street
I've been watching the dark lord carefully
It's full of danger here
Damao
Lynn brought some chocolate cakes here
Would you like some?
Uh...
We'll get something else for you next time
Just a moment ago
The dark lord tried to poison me with desserts
I'll pay for you
Just have fun
Get as many as you can
Hooray--
This one looks pretty
Look at the apple I got
Where did you get that?
Look at my strawberries
Well that's totally a cleanup
The dark lord liked strawberry-flavored souls
I'm so tired
Ira?!
I'm doing videos for three days
And drank nothing
I'm STARVING
Ira clam down
Please
Wait
Let me bite you
I'm not human
You can't drink my blood
NO——
Best man-made blood
Have a bloody good time
Boss
A cup of type B blood please
Large one with less sugar
No ice
More pearls
OK
Take it at the right
The vampire relative of the dark lord liked type B blood with pearls and no ice
Less sugar
It's impossible to win against you
I'm a game streamer though
Well
I shall go to bed now
So Ira,
How do you sleep usually
I sleep in the coffin mostly
Or hang on the window with the form of a bat
So how does Lynn sleep?
That's a problem
It must be inconvenient to sleep with the wings
Will he hang upside down like you?
I think no
Maybe standing like a horse
He is levitating???
That's AWESOME
What's happening?
Where am I?
The dark lord's feather quilt factory
The angels are here
Im' gonna cut off all of your wings
And make them in to quilts
NO——
I'm blinded!!
Sorry we'll NEVER do this again
Get away from my wings you dark lord!!
The dark lord
Even wanted to eat angel's wings
I'm hungry
Why it's full of food