Episode 24:  Farewell, my friends!
Dark lord
Neil Bowman
You came from your home alone
You thought you had friends
But what's the truth
Let me tell you
Nick
Had been bullying you since youth
Now he's getting close to you only for my power
Am I a otaku?
These two are just sharing house rent
Damao is watching you on command
They are your enemies
Is it coming to an end...
Is it raining?
No
It's not rain
Oh no
The most funny thing is
You thought you loved Lily
She's a battle angle
Born for killing me
You thought you love her wrongly
Just because of my allergy
Pathetic
So pathetic
Isn't it sad?
Painful?
There's only arrogance in this world
Selfishness
Greediness
Ignorance and laziness
Only payments
No results
Only misses
No true love
No
What's wrong
Not like you said
Neil
I know
Nick wants to save me
Wake up if you're there!
I seldom call him brother
Damn
No matter why we met for the first time
It's not Neil's fault
But
They're all my friends!
Neil
We're going to save you!
Lily
This feeling...
Is not an allergy!
Whatever you said
They'll be eliminated by me
Even if you killed them all
If the world still knows your existence
You're never going to have a peaceful life
So what?
I'm already used to it
Though I didn't know you until today
But I could feel you all the time
I know
You don't care about power
Rights
You just want to stay calmly
What did you want to say exactly
Dark lord
Could you trust me?
Their number...
Is way too big!
Damn
It ends now...?
Guys!
Neil
Neil!
I took back the control of my body temporarily
Listen to me!
All negative powers of the dark lord is released
Now
Is the best time to attack me
Neil
What are you talking about?
Ready, everyone
Aim at the dark lord
What are you doing?
It's our responsibility to defeat the dark lord
Stop arguing
It's the only way
The dark lord could gone forever
I'm saying my last words
No Neil!
Fire!
Everyone...
These times...
I'm really happy...
Impossible
I got...
Neil
Is that...
Neil!
Neil
Neil                                Neil
Everyone...
I was...
Well done Neil!
I thought I'd never see you again
Don't die Neil!!
Got it
The activity of dark lord is gone
That means...
We won!
Great!
Stop laughing
Come and help!
There are still lots of things to do
Nonsense
What if you got killed
I still have you
Pretty disgusting
Thanks for trusting me
Lynn
They're talking about the compensation
Come and have a look
OK
Dark lord has been defeated
here are the videos
Got it, will  keep watching
Coming in a second
(Do not leave yet!)
All Saints Street creator interviews
Introduce yourself
Hi, I'm the chief editor of All Saints Street, Lingzi
Favorite scene &
line in this series
My favorite scene should be the episode which Lynn carrying Lily
All the things are pretty lovely
I liked it very much
And there's a line which Lily shouted "little hole" on the snow
I think it's a very brainwashing<!-- should I tl 洗脑 like this?  >
And interesting line
Second favorite scene should be
After Damao turned into a wolf
Neil went to find him
I think that episode is full of the power of friendship
And I was touched
So that scene should be my second favorite
Which character shirt do you like
I liked all clothes of Ira's
I think they're really full of characteristics
And things like slogan on them
So I think I can bring them to reality
The second favorite might be the skirt Lily wore when she went to the park
I think it's cute
Most impressed fanart?
The most impressed fanart might be
A 1031 fan comic created by a Japanese guy on Weibo
I think... It had high completion and he worked really hard
So I was really impressed when I saw it
And another one was
Some foreign people cosplayed Damao and Ira
Because that Damao was so real
Very muscular
So I had a deep impression
And think it was interesting
What could be the plans for the future?
In the future, may be Nick will... have more salary
That's the best thing for a worker
And he will have a slightly better life than now
A gift from creator
(also one of the lyric writers)
All Saints Street
To be continued